(Howard:)What are you doing?
(Raj:)It's called Lamaze breathing.
(Raj:)It helps you push.
(Leonard:)Great.
(Howard:)He's pushing
with his uterus.
(Raj:)There's got to be a smarter way
of removing it.
(Leonard:)Yeah, this is nothing more
than a physics problem.
(Howard:)Right.
(Sheldon:)Archimedes once said,
"Give me a 'leever' long enough
"and a fulcrum
on which to place it,
and I shall move the world."
(Raj:)Of course.
(Raj:)All we need is to find stuff
to make a "leever" big
enough to fix this.
(Howard:)Exactly.
(Howard:)I'll bet there's
something around here
(Howard:)that could
be a "lehver."
Let's see, a "lehver,"
a "lehver"...
Everybody hold on!
(Sheldon:)Let's take this problem
one step at a time.
(Sheldon:)First, we need to decide
(Sheldon:)whether we're calling it
leever or lehver.
(Sheldon:)And the sooner
we decide it's leever,
(Sheldon:)the sooner we can roll up
our sleeves... not slehves...
(Sheldon:)and get to work.
(Leonard:)We're gonna be here
"foreever."